day 11 Monday I wanted to talk a little
bit about chaos like the message that
was coming up you know my stomach's in
chaos I need to eat something
uh-huh and I don't know chaos drains my
energy you wouldn't know that from the
look of my house my house is chaotic
which I know means my internal world is
chaotic and it definitely is I'd like to
look at the data and the pros and cons
and weigh things and do things from a
brain level which I'm trying to do less
of and more living for my heart it's
faster it's not easier
I was not easier but it's in the moment
it's easier overall I find it difficult
figuring out how to collectively make
sense of this chaos that we call a
planet and a life how to understand the
complexities of the issues that face us
how to stop trusting our governments and
corporations and taking that knowledge
and power back for ourselves I think is
very important so that is what I'm
working on is I mean daily I started a
list very good let's want two things on
it but a list of all the times in the
day that I I'm triggered to the wrong
word because it has a negative
connotation but like an idea sparks that
if I had this piece of knowledge what I
could do with it so I know the list in
front of me is I can't think about for
instance because of course they always
escape my minds and I have to think of
them but all the ways that we give our
data to corporations just to sell us
stuff and whatever that's not the best
use of our data it's not the worst use
of our data but it's not at that
empowering whereas I see so many ways
that our data can be used to make us
healthier to make our planet healthier
to make us more empowered and so to try
and yeah I'm just gonna keep keeping
that list I think that's a good idea
just in this moment I'm gonna get a book
that's dedicated to that and
like I just had two columns one of which
was like the piece of data and the other
one was which was like what we could
actually do with that data and when we
own our data together we own we can
decide what's collected I think I talked
about this on Friday knows that was a
whole three days ago like forever ago in
my mother mind um so yeah I don't know
what today's topics really about this
chaos this making I need it to be more
organized need the internet to be more
organized I need one place to go for
truth that isn't oh you do your research
I'll do my research will come out on
different ends understandably because
there's always research on both ends
there's always ways to point to your
side prop up your side and make it
stronger and so but be able to actually
weigh that to see how much is on the pro
side versus how much is on the con side
where does the science stand how
reliable is the science that stands on
your side and and I realized what
everything can be discussed with science
though also you know opinions from
different cultures and whatever the
discussion is finding the truth and that
doesn't mean there's one truth there can
in some instances can be multiple truths
but knowing where those come from so
that I can weigh them for myself as to
whether they have standing for me and I
highly regard science so I'm gonna have
it on that but if you listen to the
Bible then you can find your truth
related to that so yeah if you have
there's only one way to have truth I
guess this is being a very chaotic video
I'm talking about but I'm here day 11 I
might just start on this point forward
whose videos are supposed to want me
explaining the global cooperative
literally just keep explaining the
global cooperative every day all day
until one day it just works or it's like
here's what I'm doing here's what I'm
doing I wanted to explain it to hundred
different people but I also want to
hoard them like I want to not explain it
to the people who have the most power
the people who have the most money and
resources and then I
want to work with are the people I want
to talk to you last because I want to
have it perfected then right so I don't
want to hoard it and so I'm just going
to keep for the next walk today is day
12 the next 88 days just keep explaining
except when I have something amazing to
talk about on video just keep explaining
like take 37 here's the global
cooperative so that is what I will do
starting tomorrow but this is day 11
chaos getting purpose of the chaos which
maybe this video is perfect for thanks